This module will focus on
some basic strategies
to use in bull markets
when prices rise and in bear
markets when prices fall.
As you may have gathered
from earlier lessons,
the characteristics
of options requires
skill and precision when
making investment decisions.
In this module we'll
offer an explanation of
several strategies for either
type of market outlook.
We'll also walk you through
what they're designed to achieve.
We'll further provide
a practical demonstration
of how to set
up each trade using IBKR's
Trader Workstation.
By the end of this module,
you should have a clear
understanding how to use
options to plan for both
up and down markets.
Let's get started.